# JOHN MARK D. PAPELIRIN

CATBALOGAN CITY, SAMAR | papelirinjohnmarkdote@gmail.com

# **PROFILE**

I'm a Computer Engineering graduate with experience as a Technical Virtual Assistant, working with US clients on automation, Ontraport, Zapier, and web development. Comfortable working in EST time, I enjoy solving problems, meeting deadlines, and continuously learning to grow in the tech field. I'm excited to bring my skills and hands-on experience to projects that make an impact.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Seo Optimization | GoAbroad.com | Intern

Feb 2024 - May 2024

- Managed website content
- Collaborated with the development team.
- Performed data mining.

# Freelance Technical Virtual Assistant | Sister Diamonds Support December 2024- Present Services

- Built and maintained websites using Ontraport for US-based clients.
- Automated workflows and optimized processes with tools like Zapier and Ontraport.
- Supported various technical and administrative tasks, ensuring seamless project execution.

#### **SKILLS**

- Automation: Expertise in creating workflows and streamlining processes using tools like
  Ontraport and Zapier.
- Web Development: Proficient in manual coding with specialization in the MERN stack (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, Node.js), as well as developing websites using Ontraport and WordPress.
- Programming: Strong foundation in JavaScript, Node.js, and Express.js.
- SEO: Experience in optimizing website performance, fixing 404 errors, managing internal/external links, and improving image efficiency.
- UX/UI Design: Skilled in designing userfriendly interfaces and enhancing user experiences using tools like Canva and Figma.

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor of Science In Computer Engineering | Samar State University.

2020 - 2024

# **CONTACT ME**

- 09626898314
- papelirinjohnmarkdote@gmail.com
- Web Portfolio https://john-navy.vercel.app

# **REFERNCES**

#### **ALNELYN DARIA**

Executive Assistant, GoabroadInc. alnelyn.daria@goabroad.com

# Engr. Maynard r. dalemit

Assoc.Dean,CPE Program Chair, College Of Engineering 09152149011